const questions=[{
    question:"How do you print values into the console in Javascrip?  ",
    answer1:"println()",
    answer2:"ask politely",
    answer3:"console.log()",
    answer4:"create a function",
    correct:"console.log"
},
{
question:"How do you declare a class in css?",
answer1:"#container",
answer2:".container",
answer3:"container",
answer4:"all of the above",
correct:".container"
},
{
    question:"What's the semantic html tag for a img caption?",
    answer1:"<figure>",
    answer2:"<img>",
    answer3:"<header>",
    answer4:"<figcaption>",
    correct:"<figcaption>"
    },
    {
        question:"What HTML stand for?",
        answer1:"Hyper Trainer Marking Language",
        answer2:"Hyper Text Marketing Language",
        answer3:"Hyper Text Markup Language",
        answer4:"Hyper Text Markup Leveler",
        correct:"Hyper Text Markup Langauage"
        },
        {
            question:"How do you leave a comment in HTML?",
            answer1:"<!--comment-->",
            answer2:"<!-comment->",
            answer3:"<--comment-->",
            answer4:"<-comment->",
            correct:"<!--comment-->"
            },
            {
                question:"What is an example of a web API?",
                answer1:"CSS",
                answer2:"HTML",
                answer3:"Bootstrap",
                answer4:"All of the above",
                correct:"Bootstrap"
                },
                {
                    question:"What does CSS stand for?",
                    answer1:"Computer science style",
                    answer2:"Casscading Style Sheet",
                    answer3:"Coding Style Sheet",
                    answer4:"None of these",
                    correct:"Casscading Style Sheet"
                    },
                    {
                        question:"What does a boolean refer to?",
                        answer1:"a value that is true or false",
                        answer2:"a false value only",
                        answer3:"a true value only",
                        answer4:"none of the above",
                        correct:"a value that is true or false"
                        },
                        {
                            question:"What symbol signifies a class?",
                            answer1:".",
                            answer2:"#",
                            answer3:"/",
                            answer4:"=",
                            correct:"."
                            },
                            {
                                question:"What symbol signifies an id?",
                                answer1:".",
                                answer2:"#",
                                answer3:"=",
                                answer4:"/",
                                correct:"#"
                                },
]